I'm 15 for a moment Caught in between 10 and 20 and I'm just dreaming
Counting the ways to where you are I'm 22 for a moment
And she feels better than ever and we're on fire
Making her wait back for mine
15, there's still time for you Time to buy and time to sell
And I know who is 15 There's never a wish better than this
When you've only got 100 years to go
Good run, everybody. Don't forget to stretch it out.
Mr. Allman.
I, uh, I wanted to come by. If there's anything I can do...
No. There's nothing that any of us can do now.
I'm not gonna.
I'm gonna.
She really left this time of year.
You were really focused out there. Speaking as one of the dozens you passed.
I'm Lana.
Jordan Cross. I just started here a couple days ago.
Better my hair.
With my great love, biblical 교 consiste.
Alright?
Jess, you ready?
Sorry.
That's okay. There's a lot more where that came from.
I'm syrupy For you still.
Hey, nice job out there today. when you gonna join the j....
When are you gonna join the...
Mateen.
You alright?
Jordan.
The totally overwhelmed look gave you away.
I'm Clark.
Bryce, the mentor guy. Hi.
Hey, we were supposed to meet in the gymnasium.
They said you bolted. Is everything okay?
I'm still trying to get used to all these people.
I was homeschooled up until now.
Allow me to be your lifeline.
All new students are assigned a mentor.
Most importantly, because they come with a map.
Let me give you the lay of the land.
Would you mind if I checked with my dad?
Oh, sure.
I'll be right back.
It happened again, didn't it?
Jordan, I know how much you want this to work,
but I still think it's a mistake.
Not today.
Don't be today.
Jordan!
Oh!
Mr. Allman? Are you okay?
Why did you stop me?
I just... I just want to be with my little girl.
My daughter is dead and it is my fault.
I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
And I've got a job for you, too,
and this will liked it because this was a Grayman.
Something of interest?
Yes.
You should see it now.
We haven't talked in ten years,
but doing that in six months makes bucks.
hés
I'm sorry.
Schule!
COMMANDEREL!
JOHN WAYT!
DIRECTOR, SCHOOL OF LABOR!
I've been waiting for you.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Yeah, yeah, come on.
Megan, could you go and ask them if Mr. Altman's ready for visitors?
How's Mr. Altman?
He's pretty heavily sedated.
They want to keep him here until they can do a full psych evaluation.
I didn't know you and Megan knew Mr. Altman so well.
It's really through his daughter.
We were all in the cheerleading squad together back in junior high.
Mr. Altman was never the same after she died.
I remember she was hit by a car.
Yeah, walking home from her end of season party.
The doctor said that there was no chance for recovery, but, um...
that Mr. Altman kept hoping for a miracle.
Sounds like that never came.
He took her off life support last month.
I wouldn't wish that decision on anyone.
It's hard when you blame yourself for everything that happened.
I'd better go.
If I could change that night, I would.
I don't even remember why Julia and I were fighting.
Megan, don't do this.
Julia left that night because she was mad at me.
If I had just stopped her...
I wish I'd gone after her too, but, you know,
neither of us could have known what was going to happen.
You can't keep blaming yourself.
I should have told him then.
He's under sedation, I...
I'm not sure he's even hearing you.
Come on. Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
Bye.
See you.
See you tomorrow, kid.
Bye.
Uh, do you know anything you want to tell me?
I mean, actually I want to say thanks.
No, it's used up.
What is used up?
No, I don't want to do anything.
I actually have all the writability grounds.
I'm still not sure what I said there.
Go ahead.
Maybe put it back on for me.
Okay, bye.
Hey, stick to what?
He's totally insane.
Okay.
And that war doesn't even seem 100 percent real.
That was the beginning of the war.
Bye.
Hey, Jordan, it's just me.
Yeah, hi.
Just want to apologize for dropping
the mentor ball yesterday.
Mr. Altman's lucky you were there.
I just wish my dad hadn't seen it.
Just telling that Smallville High is rarely that exciting.
Trust me, my parents wrote the book on being overprotective.
You'll be just fine.
You all right?
Yeah, I just don't like being touched.
Fair enough.
What?
Nothing.
You just had that look yesterday just before Mr. Altman
jumped in front of the car.
It's almost like you knew he was going to do something.
I need some air.
Hey.
Good night.
Bye, Lana.
Bye.
It hurts!
Adam.
Are you all right?
Adam, wake up.
Get off!
Lana.
What happened?
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
You're having a king size nightmare.
I guess.
Do you want to talk about it?
To be honest, no, not really.
I'll put some clothes on.
Clean up this mess.
Clark, we've been looking all over for you.
So who gets to do the honors?
What's going on?
You ready to hear the latest news?
About Lana's house guest?
Actually, no.
No as in you're not interested?
No.
No as in it's none of my business.
Lana and I finally reset our relationship
to the friendship level.
Not going to blow up by getting between her and Adam.
Wow.
Clark's taking one for the team.
From now on, consider me an Adam-free zone.
OK.
Now that we can scratch gossip off the discussion list,
what's next on the agenda?
What?
Okay, I think we go down a track?
You're not so local.
Oh, course you are.
Nice room.
Good evening, Academic records of grand tours chosen byoure
and also shared by Robertatted by the National
Deaf Nation as a publicist, Dr. merchant.
Awesome.
Take a seat.
Come in.
Still, given your track record with Wall of Weirdness,
I think we should look into it.
Thanks.
No thanks required.
It's kind of fun being Woodward to your Bernstein again.
Lana, come in.
Your message said it was important.
Something wrong?
I was hoping you could tell me.
I understand there was an incident at the town last night.
Apparently some neighbors heard your tenants screaming.
I think that incident is a pretty strong word.
Adam had a bad dream, that's all.
It's no big deal.
And if it had been the first time, I'd probably agree with you.
What do you mean?
I can read an invoice.
Let's see.
Charges for repairing broken windows.
Replacing furniture.
All in the last week.
Is there a reason?
Why you didn't tell me?
Maybe I thought you'd jump to conclusions.
You have to admit, Adam's behavior is unusual.
And when you're on the rebound,
it's easy to let your emotions outweigh your common sense.
Look, this isn't personal.
Adam's been a real helper on the Talon.
Putting up with a few nightmares.
It's a small price to pay.
Look, it's your call.
But at the very least,
you should be able to tell me.
Don't be asking yourself.
How much do you really know about your new friend?
Right here.
Sam, here we go.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
I will.
Chloe, I think I found something.
Yeah? You and me both.
I just had a mega real-world moment with Ad...
Never mind. Sorry.
Anyway, looks like you're hammering away at the Jordan story.
Yes, I pulled this off the Ledger database.
Apparently when Jordan was six,
he went ballistic outside of a roller coaster,
screaming that someone was gonna be killed.
His dad pulled him away, but when they restarted the ride,
one of the cars broke loose.
Killing the woman standing in line with him.
Mr. Altman wasn't Jordan's first premonition.
All right, well, cue the spooky music,
because Jordan was born on the day of the meteor shower.
I took a quick trip to the courthouse
and asked them to pull up anything pertaining to Cross.
According to this, Jordan's mother died shortly after he was born.
As a result of a direct hit from the meteor?
As one life ends, another begins.
Well, that must be it.
That must be the connection.
Yeah, mix that with the meteor rocks
and you could be entering John Edward territory.
This can't be good.
That's Jordan.
Stop it!
You don't understand! I'm trying to help you!
Go away!
Megan, stop!
Please, I'm just asking you to let me walk you home.
If you don't understand, it's not what you think!
Leave me alone!
Jordan, what's going on?
I have to help her!
Why? Calm down! What's gonna happen to Megan?
She's going to die, Clark!
Don't you understand?
She's going to die!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Jordan, hold up!
My father was right, Clark.
This was a mistake.
I should have never come to school.
Jordan, I believe you.
You saw something when you touched Megan, didn't you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Like a premonition?
I don't know what you're talking about!
I know about the roller coaster.
When you touched Megan, what'd you see?
I saw fire.
Smoke.
Megan was screaming.
She couldn't breathe.
Clark, I had to warn her!
And we still can.
Megan's house is just around the corner.
These visions, when they hit, what are they like?
It's hard to describe.
It's like a...
Like curtains being pulled back.
Just long enough for me to see the moment they die.
Have you ever been able to stop one of these visions from coming true?
Never.
My dad and I did everything we could.
We called the police, the paramedics.
Begged people to take us seriously.
But no matter what we did, the visions always came true.
That's how you knew Mr. Altman was going to kill himself.
Except he survived.
Because of you.
How did you do it?
I had a vision of you too when you grabbed me in the hallway.
What do you mean? What'd you see?
Like you don't have an end like other people.
It's like you live forever.
Come on, Jordan.
You're wrong.
No.
Maybe that's why you were able to save Mr. Altman.
Nobody's ever been able to stop one of the deaths before.
Maybe you can do it again for Megan.
We'll find out.
I'm sure we'll find out.
Excuse me.
Mr. Kent.
Why am I not surprised?
Sheriff, what's happening?
We just found Megan Calder's car abandoned off the main highway.
There were signs of a struggle.
Are you Jordan Cross?
I'm told you got into an argument with Ms. Calder today.
I was just...
I was there, Sheriff.
It wasn't a big deal.
I got a missing girl, Mr. Kent.
That makes everything a big deal.
We better talk.
Thanks.
Hi.
It's a little early for your second triple cab, isn't it?
Um, actually, I came to talk to you about something.
Is Adam around?
I don't know. I haven't seen him.
I haven't seen him in a while.
You okay?
Well, I'm just...
I'm having one of those it sucks to be a reporter days.
I know you and Adam have been spending a lot of time together, but...
Chloe, what's wrong?
I'm sorry.
No, it's all good.
It's all good.
You have a problem.
Rafati?
I don't.
It's all right.
My brothers are always a band of barmen.
They live on the estates of Oh.
I didn't know the music for conseguir this kind of material receiving and
then losing power.
Oh, we don't have it.
I'm gonna throw.
Your nephew there is draw you could, I think.
I actually did.
A needs to be, every every taste for a bustle every minute, every second time I can.
He's a rich guy.
Yeah?
Well, you didn't ask me here to discuss music theory.
No.
I thought we should meet.
It's about the lamp. I'll replace it.
It's your behavior that concerns me, Adam.
Mine is a friend.
For what it's worth, we both care about Lana.
What's this?
Your colorful past.
These are my school records.
They're supposed to be sealed.
I'm not sure why you'd care.
They're exemplary.
Straight As across the board.
I was always a good student.
Actually, I spoke with your teachers.
I believe the phrases they used were,
a fine pupil and a joy to teach.
It's nice to be appreciated.
The strange thing is...
I'm not sure.
They all said it.
Word for word, almost as if they were told what to say.
Don't worry, Adam.
I'll keep checking.
We all have black marks somewhere in our past.
Jordan!
Are you all right?
I had another vision.
I thought I could help.
It's okay. Clark knows.
Wait for me in the truck.
Dad, please.
Jordan?
Excuse me.
Mr. Cross.
Jordan really wants to make a go of it at school.
Would you just give him one more chance?
I really appreciate all you've done, Clark,
but Jordan is special.
If he's at home, at least I can try to protect him.
Jordan.
Oh, my God.
Jordan!
I got your message.
In case you didn't notice, school's out.
I was at the torch doing some research.
Adam, there's no easy way to ask this,
but somebody found your needle in the trash today.
Technically, that's not a question.
Look, I'm trying to give you the benefit of the doubt.
Are you diabetic?
On some sort of medication?
Was that the research you were doing?
I mean, that would explain it, right?
Except diabetics are supposed to leave their syringes
with the school nurse.
Believe me, I am not trying to accuse you of anything.
Yes, you are.
You think I'm on drugs.
Truth is, you don't trust me.
Never have.
That's not fair.
You said you'd always be honest with me.
Why can't you be honest now?
Look, I want this to work, but if you're not sure,
just say the word, and I'm gone.
I'm gone.
Adam!
Jordan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
Hiding from my father.
I think he wants to pull me out of school.
Running away isn't going to fix that.
Jordan!
It's changed.
Jordan, what is it?
Lana, please don't leave here.
What's going on?
I can't explain it.
Something awful is about to happen.
We have to go find Clark.
Clark?
Wait.
What are you doing?
No!
Adam?
Hello?
Last I heard, breaking and entering was still against the law.
I could say the same thing to you.
Except I own the place.
I take it you have some concerns about Lana's new friend?
I think that's pretty obvious.
So what caused you to go all cloak and dagger?
Ragnar Monanoff.
When Adam came to see me earlier today,
he was playing one of his most difficult pieces.
Is that a crime?
No CDs, sheet music, not even a radio.
According to his transcripts, he never took a single music class.
So computers, kickboxing, and a master pianist.
Wow. Adam's a regular renaissance man.
Like you said, that isn't a crime.
Though it certainly piqued your interest.
Lock up on your way out.
Yeah.
All right.
Clark?
Clark, you've been looking for Jordan all over town.
I think it's time you call it a night.
Dad, I was supposed to help him fit in.
Instead, I take him to a crime scene.
I put him on the sheriff's radar.
That is not your fault.
Well, he was a lot better off before he met me.
Clark, if he ran away, it's because he didn't feel like he had anybody at home to talk to.
His dad seemed like a good man.
I'm sure he is.
And I'm also sure he feels like he's doing the best thing for Jordan.
Look, when your son has a gift,
your first temptation is to hide him away, to shelter him from everything.
You didn't.
I sure as hell wanted to.
Look, your mother convinced me that you needed to experience the whole world.
Not just this farm.
Ultimately, she was right.
So Jordan will come home.
But not until he's good and ready.
Okay?
Yeah.
All right, why don't you come on inside?
We have a bite to eat.
I'll be there in a second.
Okay.
I'll fit you down on the sex Helga other than that.
How about-
All right, I won't be holding it up.
You know, Hickory is a tough dog.
How about you?
I'm a put it away.
I'll let him out.
All right, I'll stop by later tonight.
You've had enough?
I have.
You're saying that's changed?
She was trapped in a fire, just like Megan.
Okay, okay, calm down.
What else did you see?
Stuff on the floor.
Photos burning.
Lana and Megan weren't one of them, but they were younger.
They were in cheerleading outfits.
Is this the girl?
Mr. Allman's daughter.
When I saved him, I changed everything.
Even what's supposed to happen to Lana.
Did you see anything that might tell us where she is?
Uh, there was an old sign inside.
What did it say?
It said, wandering hills.
I know where that is.
Clark, take me with you.
No way.
I've seen the house.
Maybe I can help you find it.
Please.
First sign of trouble, you back off.
Let's go.
Mr. Allman, why are you doing this?
Please, you don't have to do this.
You're gonna pay for what you did to Julia.
What are you talking about?
I heard you at the hospital.
Megan had a fight with her, and you let her leave.
You should have been looking out for her.
We didn't cause the accident.
You might as well have.
My little girl was out there all alone because of you.
It wasn't our fault.
For years, I blamed myself for not being there.
Coach, this is not the way.
But now I know.
No.
I wasn't responsible.
You two killed her.
No, I didn't.
Please.
No.
Coach, no.
Please.
Help.
Tell him we're in danger.
Anything.
Mr. Allman, help.
Following here leads to the
演 progreso's Toyotomi dataset.
Please learn 그런 code para tener more Enjoy your permanent
thought not to miss this out.
You better get out of here.
diversity based behavior was a
homework strategy.
Number of kontrol centers are
depleted with fraud and하세요 scoopassement.
Clark, look!
Jordan, stay in the car.
He's got Lana and Megan. You're going to need some help.
Stay in the car, Jordan.
Lana? Lana?
Stay with Megan.
Get out!
Jordan!
I'll get Megan.
You stay away from me!
I just want to be with my girl!
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Coach!
We've got to get out of here!
You!
It's your fault!
No!
Where's Jordan?
I didn't see him come out with us.
Clark!
Run!
Jordan!
Mr. Oldman!
Coach Oldman!
We've got to get out of here!
You can't let him get away!
You can't!
No!
Jordan.
Clark! Clark, are you okay?
Oh, my God, is he okay?
He's not breathing.
Jordan!
Come on, Jordan.
You can't die on me.
Clark.
Clark, it's okay. You're all right.
You're gonna be okay.
Lex?
Lana.
How you feeling?
Between the fire and my leg,
I've seen enough hospitals to last a lifetime.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Lex, I think you were right
about taking a closer look at Adam.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Chloe caught him using some sort of drug at school,
and when I confronted him about it,
he almost lost it.
Lana, I've had people assume the worst about me all my life.
Trust me, it's hard to respond
when people always jump to the wrong conclusions.
Like the last time we talked,
I was under the impression that you'd be happier if I kicked him out.
It's not my choice to make.
But I've had a chance to ask a few questions.
Adam hasn't been healing as well as his doctors had hoped.
Apparently he's part of a clinical medical trial,
testing his blood for a new drug.
I'm sure he's not.
He's not part of a clinical medical trial, testing a new drug.
That might explain the needle.
Doesn't explain why he was hiding it.
I'm just beginning to wonder who I let into my life.
You should trust your instincts.
Thanks, Lex.
I promise your second week at school will be easier.
Paramedics said if you hadn't given me CPR,
I'd be dead.
But you're not.
I saw her, Clark.
I saw her, Clark. Who?
My mom. In that moment,
right before you pulled me back.
She was beautiful.
I tried to run to her,
but couldn't.
Maybe it just wasn't your time.
When I woke up, they were gone.
The visions?
Maybe I was destined to lose them when I met you.
Mind if I interrupt?
Jordan, I brought your homework.
I'm sorry.
Why do I get the feeling
you've replaced me as your mentor?
I've offered to help Jordan get back on his feet,
and he is going to help me become faster on mine.
I think you're getting the hang
of this high school thing.
How you doing?
I know that look.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, Clark.
I'll see you tomorrow.
So, we've got a lot of work to do.
What's wrong?
Lana,
it's about your friend.
The one in the hall.
Adam.
He's from Oklahoma, right?
I don't know. He's never really said anything.
Jordan, what's going on?
I think something
really bad happened to him.
Well, he's been in the hospital.
He was pretty seriously injured a few months ago.
This is going to sound really strange,
but I think it's worse than that.
I don't think he was just hurt.
I think he died.
You're awfully quiet today.
Having someone tell you you can change destiny
is a lot to handle.
Yeah, Jordan's visions really struck a chord.
I just brought up questions I had all along.
Mom,
by helping Mr. Altman,
I put three other lives in jeopardy.
But you were there for them.
If it wasn't for me,
he would have never had the chance to hurt anyone.
Clark, what's this really about?
I'm just wondering
if that's why I was really sent here.
To change destiny.
What if I make a wrong choice
and I'm not there to make it right?
It's a huge responsibility.
You have to concentrate
on the good that you do.
Think of all the people you've saved.
Your dad, me, and Lex.
He's turned out to be a really good friend.
Sweetheart, you just have to do the best you can.
You can't save everybody.
Well, I'm going to take some of these out to your dad.
I'll do it.
Well, could you please make sure
that at least a couple of them
make it to the barn?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thanks, Mom.
Dad!
Dad?
Not now!
Not yet.
I love you, son.
Dad?
Mom!
Thank you.